Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records UA002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records
1918 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the University Provost and Senior Vice President
Center for the Enhancement of Learning and Teaching
UA002
128.1 Linear Feet 104 boxes
1 Artifact(s)
64 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
This collection contains the records of the Provosts of the University as well as files kept by the Office of the Provost that pre-date its existence.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of the Provost, 1998 -- 2021.
Arrangement
This collection is organized in fifteen series: Subject files 1940-1988; Subject files 1946-2013; Department files; Correspondence; General reports; Annual reports; Degrees voted; Faculty records; Committee files and annual reports; Bylaws; Sol Gittleman files; 2016-2018 accessions; David Harris files; Unprocessed accessions; and My Tufts Story video contest.
Subject files, department files and faculty records are arranged alphabetically. Correspondence, general reports, annual reports, degrees voted, committee files and annual reports, and My Tufts Story videos are arranged chronologically. Bylaws are in original order that is neither alphabetical nor chronological. Accessions are in chronological order by accession date.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of the Provost was created in 1951 after the retirement of George S. Miller from his posts of Vice President and Dean of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences at Tufts College.
After Miller's retirement, Tufts President Leonard Carmichael decided to further divide up the responsibilities of the administration to coincide with the expansion of the college. The position of provost was created to assume the academic administrative duties covered by Miller when he was Vice President. The new provost was expected to oversee the academic affairs of the institution, especially faculty appointments and curriculum problems. The provost also serves as chair of the Academic Council.
In 1953, after original provost John P. Tilton was elected Senior Vice President, the position was renamed Senior Vice President and Provost. The change in the title added control over not only the academic and financial affairs of the university, but also made the provost the immediate assistant to and stand in for the president.
Tilton, the first provost, served from 1951 until his untimely death in 1959. A month later, Leonard Mead was named to the post, and served until 1965. Mead was succeeded by Albert Ullman, who held the position until 1973. After Ullman's retirement, Tufts named Kathyrn McCarthy to the position, making her the first female provost. McCarthy resigned in 1979, citing differences with the administration on the direction of the university. After her resignation, the university conducted a nationwide search for a replacement, and in 1981 hired Tufts professor Sol Gittleman, at the time the chair of the Department of German and Russian Languages. After serving in the position for over 21 years - a tenure believed to be the longest in American higher education at the time - Gittleman stepped down from this post in 2002. He continues to teach and pursue research at Tufts as University Professor.
Jamshed Bharucha was appointed Provost and Senior Vice President of Tufts University in August of 2002. As of summer 2006, Provost Bharucha has been active with starting the Summer Scholars program, the Provost's Fellows program and the Graduate Competitiveness Initiative and in increasing faculty recruitment and development, successfully bringing accomplished scholars and leaders as new Deans to Tufts.
Related Materials
University Microfilm Collection, 1878 -- 1985. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Sol Gittleman Papers, 1966 -- 2015. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the records of the Provosts of the University as well as files kept by the Office of the Provost that pre-date its existence, including subject files and correspondence from various Provosts, departmental reports to the Provost, and bylaws of Tufts' schools and the Board of Trustees. This collection also contains faculy records, including appointment records, tenure information, and curriculum vitae; information about degree requirements voted on by the Board of Trustees; annual summary reports submitted by the Provost to the University President as well as reports submitted by Deans, Chairs, and ad hoc committees to the Provost; general reports created both within the university and by external consultants rearding long-range planning and feasibility studies; and student films created for the My Tufts Story video contest.
For reports issued by the Office of the Provost to the President, see "Annual Reports." For reports issued by departments to the Office of the Provost, see "Department Records." For reports issued by committees within Tufts to the Office of the Provost, see "Committee files and annual reports."
Separated Materials
Personal files of Sol Gittleman removed to form MS232 Sol Gittleman Papers.
Tufts University -- History; Administration and Governance -- Governance; Administration and Governance -- Planning, evaluation, policies & procedures; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty
- Subject files, 1940 -- 1988; 1943 -- 1982; UA002.001; 13.2 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains subject files of the Office of the Provost including material from John P. Tilton (1951-59), Leonard C. Mead (1959-65), Albert D. Ullman (1965-73), Kathryn McCarthy (1973-79), Robert B. Shira (1979-81), and Sol Gittleman (1981-2002).
  This series contains subject files of the Office of the Provost from the first accession. The original accession of subject file materials for this collection was arranged in one series titled "Subject Files, 1843-82." This included materials from several provost administrations. When a subsequent accession containing Sol Gittelman records was received in the1980s, a decision was made to create a separate series for each provost. A second subject file series was created at the time. However, subsequent accessions indicated that records of different provosts were not maintained separately in the Office of Provost and significant overlap occurred across administrations. As of summer 2006, archivists decided not to create a new series for each provost. Rather, each new accession will be added to Series 2. This means that each new run of subject files will be arranged alphabetically, and accessions will most likely overlap chronologically reflecting administrative use.
  There is significant overlap in the types of records contained in "Subject Files" (boxes 1-21), "Department Files" (boxes 22-26), and "Correspondence" (boxes 27-30). The files contain correspondence and reports similar to materials found in other series.
  As of July 2006, it was decided to not reprocess these old files but to prevent this kind of overlap in the future. For reports issued by the Office of the Provost to the President as well as reports from Deans and Chairs to the Provost, see "Annual Reports." For reports issued by departments to the Office of the Provost, see "Department Records." For reports issued by committees within Tufts to the Office of the Provost, see "Committee files and annual reports."
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - A and S correspondence, 1977 -- 1980; UA002.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - AAUP, 1972; UA002.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - AAUP, 1969 -- 1971; UA002.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - AAUP, 1967 -- 1968; UA002.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - AAUP, 1966; UA002.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - AAUP, 1964 -- 1965; UA002.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - AAUP, 1943 -- 1963; UA002.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - AAUP: Taylor case, 1961 -- 1967; UA002.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - AAUP: Taylor case, 1967 -- 1968; UA002.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - AFROTC, 1965 -- 1970; UA002.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - AICUIM, 1981; UA002.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Academic audit, 1985; UA002.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Academic council, 1970 -- 1982; UA002.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation, 1966; UA002.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation, 1966; UA002.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation, 1970; UA002.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation, 1970; UA002.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation, 1982; UA002.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Accrediting, 1972 -- 1982; UA002.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Accrediting: arts & sciences, 1970 -- 1980; UA002.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Accrediting: dental school, 1985; UA002.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Accrediting: engineering, 1964 -- 1975; UA002.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Accrediting: NCATE, 1967; UA002.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Ad hoc geriatric committee, 1978; UA002.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Administration, 1971 -- 1976; UA002.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Administration, 1967; UA002.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Administration committee, 1979; UA002.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Administration committee: arts & sciences, 1972 -- 1978; UA002.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Administration committee: NEMC, 1979; UA002.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Admissions, 1977 -- 1982; UA002.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Admissions, 1970 -- 1976; UA002.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Admissions: Jackson, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Admissions: liberal arts and engineering, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American affairs, 1969; UA002.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American center, 1970 -- 1978; UA002.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Alcoholic beverages, campus use of, 1959 -- 1963; UA002.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Allied health, 1970 -- 1977; UA002.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Allied health training, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Alumni relations, 1970 -- 1981; UA002.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Annual reports, 1971 -- 1980; UA002.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Association of Urban Universities, 1970 -- 1972; UA002.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Athletics, 1970 -- 1976; UA002.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Attendance, 1955 -- 1973; UA002.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Audiovisual resource committee, 1969 -- 1979; UA002.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Ballou Hall, 1955 -- 1976; UA002.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Barber, Dr. William, 1966 -- 1968; UA002.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Biology department, 1972 -- 1976; UA002.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Board of visitors, 1966 -- 1967; UA002.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1966 -- 1977; UA002.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1966 -- 1977; UA002.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1966 -- 1977; UA002.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Boston tech proposal, 1975; UA002.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Boston tech proposal, 1975; UA002.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Boston tech proposal, 1972 -- 1976; UA002.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Boston tech project, 1974 -- 1975; UA002.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Boston tech project, 1975; UA002.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Bradford proposal, 1978; UA002.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Braitmayer foundation, 1971 -- 1974; UA002.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Business office, 1980 -- 1983; UA002.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Business office, 1976 -- 1979; UA002.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Business office, 1970 -- 1976; UA002.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Bylaws: arts & sciences, 1953 -- 1962; UA002.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Campaign for Tufts, 1980 -- 1985; UA002.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Campus planning, 1970 -- 1977; UA002.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Campus police, 1979; UA002.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Center for Environmental Management, 1988; UA002.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Chairmen, 1956 -- 1977; UA002.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Chaplain, 1975 -- 1979; UA002.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Chemical engineering, 1970 -- 1981; UA002.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Churchill scholarships, 1964 -- 1969; UA002.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - College Within, 1970 -- 1976; UA002.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - College Within, 1970 -- 1971; UA002.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - College Within, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Chaplain search, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - College Within, 1973; UA002.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Columbia Point, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Commencement, 1978 -- 1984; UA002.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Commencement, 1940 -- 1981; UA002.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Commencement, 1971 -- 1977; UA002.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Committee on International Education, 1968; UA002.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Committees: ad hoc committee to formulate faculty policy with respect to student publications, 1964 -- 1965; UA002.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Committees: advistory committee on faculty personnel, 1940 -- 1969; UA002.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Committees: Archives, 1968; UA002.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Committees: art gifts, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Committees: biological sciences, 1976; UA002.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Committees: biomedical engineering, 1964 -- 1965; UA002.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Committees: civil engineering, 1970 -- 1977; UA002.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Committees: computer facilities and usage, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Committees: corporation visiting committees, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Committees: equal educational opportunities, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Committees: long range planning, 1968 -- 1969; UA002.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Committees: long range planning, 1970 -- 1973; UA002.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Committees: oceanography, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Committees: oceanography, 1971; UA002.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Committees: President's advisory council on minority and women's affairs, 1971 -- 1977; UA002.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Committees: standing committees, 1968 -- 1969; UA002.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth proposal fund, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth Fund Proposal, 1975 -- 1977; UA002.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth Fund Proposal, 1974 -- 1977; UA002.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth Fund Proposal, 1976; UA002.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth Fund Proposal, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund Proposal, 1978; UA002.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund Proposal, 1978; UA002.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund Proposal, 1974 -- 1978; UA002.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund Proposal, 1977 -- 1981; UA002.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1981 -- 1982; UA002.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Communications status report, 1985; UA002.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Community health, 1974 -- 1979; UA002.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Community health, 1971; UA002.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Community health proposal, UA002.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
    No Date Available
  - Community relations, 1970 -- 1977; UA002.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Computer priority committee, 1976 -- 1980; UA002.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Computer services, 1977 -- 1981; UA002.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Computer services, 1975; UA002.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Computer services, 1972 -- 1974; UA002.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Computers, 1972 -- 1977; UA002.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Computers: general, 1963 -- 1972; UA002.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Conference Bureau, 1978; UA002.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Consulting policy, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Continuing education, 1976 -- 1979; UA002.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Controller's report: fiscal year ending 30, 1906 -- 1983; UA002.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Cooperative activities, 1974 -- 1977; UA002.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Cooperative activities, 1968 -- 1974; UA002.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Counseling, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Cousens complex, 1977; UA002.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Crane Theological School, 1966 -- 1978; UA002.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Crane Theological School, 1965 -- 1967; UA002.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Curators, 1969; UA002.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Day care, 1971 -- 1973; UA002.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Day care, 1969; UA002.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - de Burlo, 1970 -- 1981; UA002.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - de Burlo, 1962 -- 1969; UA002.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Dean of students/student affairs, 1967 -- 1980; UA002.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Decision making center, 1976 -- 1982; UA002.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Dedications, cornerstones, plaques, 1954 -- 1968; UA002.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Degree requirements revision, 1985; UA002.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Delta Health Center, 1968 -- 1973; UA002.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Dental dean search committee, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1975 -- 1983; UA002.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1976; UA002.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1976; UA002.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1975; UA002.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1975; UA002.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1974; UA002.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1971 -- 1973; UA002.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1971 -- 1973; UA002.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1970; UA002.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1968 -- 1969; UA002.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Dental school, 1967 -- 1968; UA002.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Dining services, 1972 -- 1982; UA002.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Disadvantaged groups, 1964 -- 1968; UA002.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Drama department, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Dunn, Jack, 1971 -- 1981; UA002.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Economic department: report to visiting committee, 1985; UA002.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Economic department: reorganization, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Educational media, 1981; UA002.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - EEO search, 1976 -- 1978; UA002.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Endowment and annuity funds, 1981; UA002.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Energy Congress, 1976 -- 1978; UA002.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Engineering, 1951 -- 1968; UA002.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Engineering management, 1975 -- 1977; UA002.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Engineering task force, 1974; UA002.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Engineering task force, 1974; UA002.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Equipment inventory and space utilization guide, 1982; UA002.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Exam schedules, 1976; UA002.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Examinations, 1955 -- 1965; UA002.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Experimental College, 1970 -- 1975; UA002.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Experimental College, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Faculty annual, 1966 -- 1968; UA002.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Faculty appointments, orientation and workloads, 1963 -- 1981; UA002.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Faculty club, 1962 -- 1967; UA002.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Faculty EPC, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Faculty evaluations and commitment, 1949 -- 1966; UA002.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Faculty evaluations and commitment, 1966; UA002.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Faculty handbook, 1960 -- 1974; UA002.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Faculty "moonlighting,", 1965 -- 1968; UA002.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Faculty salary statistics, 1975 -- 1980; UA002.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Fees, 1955 -- 1979; UA002.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Fellowships (Woodrow Wilson), 1960 -- 1965; UA002.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Financial aid, 1980 -- 1982; UA002.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - FInancial aid, 1977 -- 1979; UA002.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Financial aid, 1971 -- 1977; UA002.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Financial aid, 1966 -- 1970; UA002.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Financial aid, 1966 -- 1970; UA002.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Financial aid, 1961 -- 1962; UA002.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Financial report: fiscal year, 1984; UA002.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher School, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher School, 1968 -- 1969; UA002.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher School, 1978; UA002.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher School, 1977; UA002.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher School, 1975 -- 1977; UA002.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher School, 1975 -- 1977; UA002.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School, 1974; UA002.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School, 1974; UA002.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School, 1972; UA002.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School, 1972; UA002.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School, 1970 -- 1972; UA002.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School, 1970 -- 1972; UA002.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School, 1966 -- 1967; UA002.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School: dean search, 1977; UA002.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher YRO, 1974; UA002.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Fraternities, 1961 -- 1976; UA002.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Fraternities, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Fuel performance, 1973 -- 1975; UA002.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Fundraising drives, 1975 -- 1981; UA002.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Funds for use by the university, 1970 -- 1977; UA002.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Future of the graduate school, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Gifts to the campus, 1956 -- 1968; UA002.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Governance, 1967 -- 1971; UA002.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Government resources, 1977; UA002.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Government resources, 1979 -- 1983; UA002.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Government resources, 1975 -- 1979; UA002.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Government resources, 1973 -- 1975; UA002.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Government resources, 1973 -- 1975; UA002.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Grades, 1970 -- 1981; UA002.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Grades, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Grading system, 1953 -- 1964; UA002.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Graduate school, 1973 -- 1975; UA002.001.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Graduate school, 1968 -- 1972; UA002.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Graduate school, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Graduate school, 1966 -- 1967; UA002.001.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Graduate school, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Grafton campus, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Grievance procedures, 1975 -- 1977; UA002.001.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Grievance procedures, 1975; UA002.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Grounds and buildings, 1971 -- 1978; UA002.001.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Health science development, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.001.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Health services committee, 1978 -- 1980; UA002.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - HEW department, 1970 -- 1980; UA002.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Higher education facilities, 1966 -- 1967; UA002.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Housing, 1977; UA002.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Human subjects committee, 1972 -- 1980; UA002.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Humanic Design Division, 1974 -- 1976; UA002.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Humanistic studies, 1969 -- 1970; UA002.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Innauguration of Jean Mayer, 1976; UA002.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Institutional planning, 1981 -- 1983; UA002.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Insurance, 1978 -- 1980; UA002.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Insurance, 1959 -- 1966; UA002.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Integrated studies program, 1974 -- 1978; UA002.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Integrative planning, 1980; UA002.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Intercultural center, 1977 -- 1981; UA002.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Internal Management Group, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.001.008.00015 (Box 8)